Hey, I just got a text
from Charles, y'all.
He got on the wrong bus.
He's on the other side of town.
Other side of town?
But our concert is in an hour.
Yeah, I know, but he wants us to warm up
and rehearse
Praise to the Lord.
Charles said that?
- In text.
- Okay, okay.
Well, if that's what Charles said—
Yeah, that's okay.
We got this.
- We can do this.
We can do this.
Come on, y'all.
♪ Five, six, seven, eight
♪ We lift up to the Lord
♪ We give praise up to the Lord ♪
♪ We sing merrily up to the Lord ♪
♪ Give thanks up to the Lord
♪ We lift up to the Lord
♪ We give praise up to the Lord ♪
♪ We sing merrily up to the Lord ♪
♪ Give thanks up to the Lord
♪ I think you're off of your note ♪
♪ You're going higher than your note ♪
♪ Pretty sure this is my note ♪
♪ In fact, I'm positive this is my note ♪
♪ Because this is my note
♪ Pretty sure this is my note ♪
♪ Could have sworn this was your note ♪
♪ That has never been my note ♪
♪ Well, we can't have the same note ♪
♪ So one of us is wrong
♪ Why don't you worry about your note? ♪
♪ I'll take care of my own note ♪
♪ But it's a really,
really, really bad note ♪
♪ You are not Charles
♪ I never said that I was Charles ♪
♪ Well, you're acting
like you think you're Charles ♪
♪ Look, I know that I'm not Charles ♪
♪ You can say that again
♪ Well, you're both off your notes ♪
♪ And it's messing
with the rest of our notes ♪
♪ Speak for yourself, Nyema,
I'm holding my note ♪
♪ I wasn't trying to single you out ♪
♪ You said everyone was off their notes ♪
♪ Not everything is about you, Gina ♪
Huh.
♪ Kiss my black ass!
♪ Oh, dear Lord
♪ Where is
♪ Charles?
- This don't make no sense.
- Come on, man.
Well, that was a good one.
Gotta release the Africa.
Yeah, you just got to get
those short bursts of song,
so you can run away before
are trying to genocide your.
Mm, that's why—
That's when you get those—
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's the guy that...
Did not make it out.
- That's, like, Swahili for "Get me out—
- I'm hit!"
"Where'd y'all motherfuckers go?"
Yeah.
You know what I'm talking about?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Ah!
Ahh.
Yeah, uh.
Ha ha ha!
Oh, no.
Uh...
Oh.
Oh... ah!
Wha—ah, ah?
Huh.
Ah.
Uh...
Ah?
Ah—uh...
Uh...
Ah. Ah.
Ah.
Ah!
Oh.
Jordan, would you say
I'm gullible?
Mm... no.
I feel sometimes like I'm gullible.
So you believed me when I said
that you weren't gullible just now?
- Oh, darn it. Okay.
- See what happened?
Wait a minute, so then,
what else is not true
that you told me?
Are you not Danny Glover's son?
No, would I be able to talk
like this if I wasn't
Danny Glover's son?
That's a really good point.
You wouldn't be able
to talk like that if you weren't...
Danny Glover's son.
I can't help talking like this.
Hey, man.
You gotta let me out of here.
Oh, okay.
You tricked me.
I can honestly say
I wasn't trying to trick you.
You weren't?
All I said was, "You gotta
let me out of here."
There's no trick.
So I do have to let you out of here?
Yes?
Okay.
Bon voyage.
Order's to let him go,
I don't know why
he's in here in the first place.
I don't know.
Sorry.
Boy, you really got me in trouble.
Yeah, you must think
I'm stupid.
Well, I'm not stupid.
I'm smart, so—
You know how you could prove
that you're really smart?
Oh, yeah, let me guess.
You want me to let you out of here again.
- Well.
- You know what?
You think that you can trick me
into letting you out again.
Well, you can't.
'Cause this is my choice.
- Get the heck out of here.
- All right.
All right?
Reverse psychology.
Sorry about that, guys.
That was me, guys, my bad.
My bad.
Real nice.
Now they said they're gonna
dock my pay, and if I let you
out of here again,
I'm gonna be severely punished.
I mean, what are you gonna do?
I'm actually surprised
they haven't already
thrown you in here with me.
No, prison is for bad guys.
You're a bad guy, and I'm a good guy.
Yeah, but you could see how,
from my perspective,
I'm a good guy.
Wait, you're a good guy?
It doesn't seem like you
understand what your job is.
Oh, oh, okay.
I see what you're doing.
You're trying to manipulate me
with reverse psychology.
- Well, it's not gonna work.
- No.
It's not even worth going out there again.
Look, they just gon' get me
and bring me back in here,
just like they always do.
Unless...
What?
No, I'm—
Forget it, I don't want
to take advantage of you anymore.
Look, hey, no, no, listen.
I'm not gonna fall for it,
whatever it is.
You may as well just tell me.
I was just gonna say that,
like, if you were to help me...
Uh-huh.
Get past the guards...
Yeah, yeah.
And get all the way out—
Okay.
I really—
No, I have to tell you.
You need to think
about this long and hard.
Weigh your options and consider
the ramifications of those options.
Like heck I will.
- Let's go.
- All right.
- I'm busting you outta here!
- Shh.
Don't—don't yell, man.
You might as well ring the alarm.
- Good idea, yeah.
- No—
Look, look, he—ah!
He's—
- Oh, hi, Tom.
- It was—
- Good to see you guys.
- Yeah.
Oh, boy, I did it again, didn't I?
It's actually very ironic,
'cause when I was
a prison guard—
When I was a prison guard,
I wasn't allowed to talk to the prisoners.
That was the thing, they said to me,
"If you talk to those prisoners,
you're gonna get in trouble.
You're gonna get in trouble."
Now that I'm in here with you,
I can talk as much as I want.
Just babble on, and babble on,
and babble on, we can talk about
anything you want. Any—any—
Teaching Center is brought to you by BMW.
The ultimate driving machine.
Hello and welcome to Teaching Center.
I'm Boyd Maxwell, with today's top stories
from the exciting world of teaching.
And I'm Perry Schmidt.
Well, now we know.
The long awaited announcement
by star English teacher
Ruby Ruhf has sent teaching fans
across the nation into a frenzy.
I've enjoyed my time in Ohio very much,
but I'm pleased to announce
that I'm taking my talents
back to New York City.
Thank you very much.
Apparently, PS431 has made Ruby
an offer she couldn't refuse.
$80 million guaranteed over six years,
with another $40 million in incentives
based on test scores.
This salary puts her right up there
with Rockridge Elementary's
Katie Hope
and William Wu out of—
Colgate Magnet!
All right, let's take a look
at yesterday's
high school teacher draft
from Radio City Music Hall,
where Central Rapids High,
recipient of the worst
test scores last semester,
made the first pick
that was no surprise to anyone.
For the first pick,
Central Rapids High takes...
Calculus teacher Mike Yoast
from Tulsa Teacher's College.
And just like that,
you're a millionaire. Ha ha.
Mike Yoast is an unbelievable story,
his father living
from paycheck to paycheck
as a humble pro football player.
Kid was a natural mathlete.
You know he's gonna buy his mom a house.
- Oh, you know this.
- Oh, there's no way
around that.
You owe your mom.
Today's highlight of the day
is brought to you
by the 100% Black Angus Beef
Thickburger
on a fresh-baked bun
from Carl's Jr. and Hardee's.
Now it's time
for the highlight of the day.
Star history teacher
Ashley Ferguson has been
running up them test scores
over at Vinz Clortho High.
- Okay.
- Whoo.
Confederate forces fired first.
Can anyone tell me
where this battle took place?
Now, look at this.
She looks left, then right,
looks past the students
with their arms up in the air,
spots Max near the back...
Whoo.
Sees that even though his hand
isn't up, he's engaged.
Max?
It was Fort Sumter?
That's right.
Oh, come on.
See what she did there?
She's bringing a introvert
into the discussion, y'all.
That's a teacher of the year
play right there.
That's right, Boyd.
You know, the confidence gained
by Max by answering
that question correctly
will enhance his performance
throughout the rest of the year.
No doubt.
Coming up after the break,
Mayfield Prep trades
French teacher Janeane Lowe
to Skyline High for a head librarian
and two lunch ladies to be named later.
And we'll get the inside scoop
on the impending
- teacher's strike that could...
- Uh-oh.
Cripple the season.
Next up, on Teaching Center.
Whoo.
Strength courses through me.
I am velocity.
I am power.
I am a leader, a believer.
I am the force that guides.
I am the gateway to what is possible,
the path to the future.
I am the future.
The all-new 2015 six Series is here.
Meet the new Teacher's Pet.
You know what?
I'm not gon' be—
I'm not gonna be doing no commercials.
- None?
- I'm not gonna sell
my out.
I'm gonna keep my integrity.
That's good, 'cause that way,
you don't have to ever worry
about buying a car or anything like that.
But what, just for argument's sake,
what kind of figures
are people getting these days?
Well, like, if it was a Sam—
You know, maybe Samsung or something,
you might make $750,000,
or something like that.
750...
Yeah, yeah.
- Thousand.
- I mean, you'd have to give up
- your phone—your iPhone.
- I'm in.
- What?
I don't think there's an offer
on the table, or anything.
Let's find one.
Well, what about your, um,
artistic integrity?
$750,000.
750, 500.
- What would you—would you—
- 250.
Take it easy.
Now, wait a second.
We'll do it together.
Okay, yeah, but we wouldn't just do
a commercial for anybody, now.
- We wouldn't do it for anybody.
- Sss...
- I mean, if, you know—
- If they got $100,000 I am.
Okay, let's say that the Ku Klux Klan came
for us to do a commercial.
For $100,000?
Well, they're giving
back to the black community
at that point—
Me.
- Best comic book adaptation...
- Oh, yeah.
- To film hand down.
- It's—oh, yeah.
- No argument.
- Oh, yeah.
Oh.
See you later, girls.
- All right.
- Oh, yeah.
Um, I know I'm in the minority
here, but I don't really like
the Christopher Nolan
Batman movies.
I don't.
I really just feel like they're... overrated.
Okay.
Well, that's, um, that's just an opinion.
You see, that's why
I prefaced it by saying,
"I know I'm in the minority."
Awkward.
You know, what, no.
No.
Not really.
It's not awkward,
at least not until you said "awkward."
Now it's awkward,
because of what you said.
Anyway.
Anyway, what?
Really, 'cause when you say "anyway,"
then you have to follow it up
with an actual contribution
to the conversation we're having.
- Yikes.
- No, look at me.
Look at me. Look at me.
There's no "yikes," and the reason why
there's no "yikes" is,
there's nothing scary
about this situation, okay?
It's a very low-stakes situation.
All right.
No, not "all right."
Come here. No.
Don't look at him. Don't look
at either of those guys.
Look at me, all right?
"All right," what?
'Cause after you say "all right,"
you have to follow that up with something.
Don't do it.
Don't look at them.
Do not look at them.
- No—
- No. Do not look at them.
Do not look at them.
Don't do it.
Tell us how you really feel.
Okay, you know what?
I'll tell you how I really feel.
Listen, I really feel
like you're an asshole
who has nothing interesting to say.
So what—oh.
No. Don't.
No, don't look at them.
Turn your head.
Turn it.
Right here.
Tell me an opinion
that you have about something.
Just one opinion that you have
about anything at all.
Just share an opinion.
Anything. Share an opinion.
Share an opinion.
Share an opinion right now.
Just off the top of your head.
Share an opinion.
Anything.
Just one opinion, that's all I'm asking.
Share one opinion right now.
- Share it. Share an opinion.
- Ah, ah, ah...
I don't have an opinion,
and that's why I just like
everything that everyone else
likes in pop culture.
Don't look at me.
Don't look at me!
Okay.
Can you recall the last place
you felt out of place?
I feel a little out of place
everywhere, to be honest, like—
Mm, that's the mark of a genius.
I... can't say
I disagree with you.
But... these equations
happening in my head, these...
Oh, boy.
What have I done?
Ideas—nay, concepts.
♪ I'm gonna do my one line here ♪
Oh, yeah.
Ra!
Ya, ya?
You can just use English
when you're talking to me, man.
Okay, listen to me.
I'm just saying,
all I did was enhance the bit.